

ASAD KHAN Graphic designer

asadgorsi76@gmail.com



+92 321 8820567



About me



Hi There. I'm Asad Khan, I'm an expert graphic designer ready to bring your vision to life. From logos to websites, I offer professional and high-quality design services for all your needs. Trust me to elevate your brand and take it to the next level.

Personal skills



- > Sociability
- > Punctuality
- > Creativity
- > Positivity
- > Gaming

Languages



URDU		100%
ENG		90%

Professional Skills



Adobe Illustrator	100%
Adobe Photoshop	100%
Adobe Indesign	95% ₹
Corel-Draw	100%
Adobe After Effect	95%
Adobe Premiere Pro	95% ₹
Blender	95%

Experience



Graphic Designer

June 2017 - Dec 2017

CoreSolution&Services

I have worked in CoreSolution&Services for 6 months as a Interne. It was a great experience.

Graphic Designer

Junuary 2018 - June 2019

ArtBox by Naba

I have worked in ArtBox by Naba for 18 months as a Graphic Designer. It was a printing company. I have learned so much from there.

Graphic Designer

April 2021 - March 2023

WeCustomBoxes

I was working in WeCustomBoxes as a Senior Graphic Designer. It's a International Printing company.

FreeLance Designer

April 2019

Fiverr.com

I am currently working as a Freelance graphic Designer on Fiverr.com. I am a Level 1 Seller on Fiverr. It is an online Platform where many people come looking for different skills.

Education



F.A
Allama Igbal Open University

i completed my F.A from AlOU.

Graphic Design Course

2020

2022

Linkedin.com

I have completed my Graphic Design Course from Linkedin.com. The course was divided into 11 Points each describe thoroughly.

Graphic Design Course

2019

Digiskills.pk

I have completed my Graphic Design Course from digiskills.pk. An online institute. The duration of the course was 3 months with weekly Assignments for practice.

Graphic Design Course

2017

Brains Group of Collages

I have completed my Graphic Design Course from Brains Group of Collages. The duration of the course was 3 months with monthly Assignments for practice.

Hobbies



